(Transcribed by TurboScribe.ai. Go Unlimited to remove this message.) Little Fox The Tale of Jemima Puddle Duck
Episode 3 Nine Eggs The fox led Jemima
to his shed.
Jemima looked inside.
Hmm, said Jemima.
Why are there so many feathers in there?
The fox didn't answer.
It does look warm and cozy, said Jemima.
So Jemima went in.
She gathered straw and feathers.
Soon she had a nice warm nest.
I'll be back tomorrow, she said.
I'll take care of your nest, said the
fox.
You're so kind, said Jemima.
Thank you.
Each day, Jemima came to the shed.
She went inside and laid an egg.
Then she went home in the evening.
Jemima went to bed.
Each night, the fox counted the eggs.
He turned them over and smiled.
They're so big, he said.
They look delicious.
At last, nine eggs filled the nest.
I'm done, Jemima said.
I'll be back tomorrow.
Then I'll stay until my eggs hatch.
Wonderful, said the fox.
He licked his lips.
Please bring some herbs tomorrow, he said.
I will cook a big dinner for us.